

SULTAN KAUTSAR

TECH ENTHUSIAST

I'm an Information Technology undergraduate student who is enthusiastic about technology and web developing. I enjoy working in a team and being able to communicate with each other. I have expertise in technical and analytical fields. I apply it to my agency business.

EDUCATION

2019 - Present

TELKOM UNIVERSITY

S1 Information Technology

2016 - 2019

MERTOYUDAN 1 HIGH SCHOOL

Natural Science

SKILL

- Cloud Engineer (Google Cloud Platform)
- Google Document Processing
- Technical Support
- Website Creation
- Communications
- Business Development
- · Working In Team

CONTACT

- 0812 2545 9071
- 😭 me@sultankautsar.com
- sultankautsar.com
- in linkedin.com/in/sultankautsar

EXPERIENCE

2022 - Present

Bangkit Cloud Computing

- Operating Google Cloud Platform
- Build Backend for Web and Mobile
- Write API Documentation
- Idea Generation and MVP Planning
- Startup Valuation and Investment Pitch
- Adaptability and Critical Thinking

2020 - Present

Rayatiga Agency

- Installing a WordPress web to the user.
- Provide web specification recommendations to users.
- Provide technical support about what is experienced by the user.
- Maintain database and user accounts on hosting.

HOBBY

- Analyzing Business (e.g. advertising, etc)
- Writing Letter or Documentation
- Regular Excercise (Sport)
- Read/watch technology updates
- Playing a Guitar (esp. jazz)